《鬼娃回魂5：鬼娃孽种》
日本制造
Made in Japan
这是我一生中见过最丑的东西
That's the ugliest thing I've ever seen in my whole life.
确实是 谁送的？
It certainly is, Who sent it?
很奇怪 上面没想写 能是谁送的呢？
That's strange, it doesn't say.Who could've come from?
我不喜欢它 它老盯着我
I don't like it.It's staring at me.
可能是你叔叔的一个恶作剧吧
It's probably one of your uncle's jokes.
我可不认为这有意思
I don't think it's funny at all.
亲爱的 我去洗个澡
Darling, I'm just going to have a shower.
我马上过去
Be there in a minute.
克劳迪娅 我告诉过你别乱扔玩具
Claudia, I told you not to leave your toys lying about.
好家伙 你可真吓人
Good God! You are hideous.
克劳迪娅
Claudia.
干嘛？
What?
我们可有言在先的 小丫头
I have a bone to pick you with you, young lady.
我们之前不是说好的吗？是吗？
We had an agreement, didn't we?
是不是？
Didn't we?
但是 老爸 我没有把它放在那里
But, Daddy, I didn't leave it there.
在文明社会里 说话要算话的
In a civilized society, our word is our bond.
我听不懂你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
就算是你生日
Just because it's your birthday,
那你也不能为所欲为
that doesn't mean that you can relinquish all…
理查德？
Richard?
理查德 什么声音？
Richard, what was that?
你杀了我的妈妈和爸爸
You killed my mommy and daddy.
现在你又尿裤子了
And now you're pissing your pants!
你尿裤子了 你尿裤子了
You're pissing your pants! You're pissing your pants!
醒醒 你尿裤子了
Wake up! You're pissing your pants!
女士们 先生们
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
你们期待已久的
what you've all been waiting for
丑脸
Shitface!
还有全英国最优秀的口技家…
And the greatest ventriloquist in all of England:
疯子伯塞斯
The psychotic Psychs!
（伯塞斯&丑脸）
（英国皇家国际口技大赛 格拉斯顿伯里 英格兰）
这个令人生厌的小怪物
This grotesque abomination…
它在生理结构上有一些异常
He ain't even anatomically correct.
别笑
Don't laugh.
这是病
It's a serious condition.
六年前 我在州立公墓里发现了它
Six years ago, I found it in a cemetery back in the States.
这小崽子试图扯破我的喉咙
Little fucker tried to rip me throat out.
我当时是想给你个拥抱
I was trying to give you a hug.
我对自己知之甚少
I don't know much about myself.
我知道自己是个孤儿
I know I'm an orphan.
我知道自己是个怪胎
I know I'm a freak.
当然 我还知道我是个日本货
And, of course, I know that I'm Japanese.
但是为何我会做那么可怕的梦？
But why do I have such terrible nightmares?
充满着仇恨 血腥和内脏
Filled with hate and blood and guts.
我一点都不喜欢这样
I'm not like that at all.
我甚至都不会伤害一只苍蝇
I wouldn't even hurt a fly.
哦 它飞走了 去找它的家人
Oh, there he goes, back to his family.
哦 真让我羡慕
Oh, I envy him.
有时 我真想知道我父母是谁
Sometimes I wonder about my own parents.
他们是禅宗大师吗？
Were they Zen masters?
他们祀奉天皇吗？
Did they serve the emperor?
哦 有时我真想知道我父母长什么样子
Oh, sometimes I wonder what my mom and dad were really like.
看来 你不相信有圣诞老人？
So, you don't believe in Santa Claus?
那么 相信我 亲爱的 今晚我就会让你相信的
Well, trust me, honey, tonight I'm going to make you believe.
你就等着瞧圣诞老人带什么给你吧 顽皮的小丫头
You wait and see what Santa is bringing you, you naughty girl.
不 我能听见你 你没断线
No, I can hear you fine. You're not breakin' up.
瑟艾拉 我刚才说你没有断线
Sheila, I just said you're not breakin' up.
哦
Oh.
你要和我分手？
You're breaking up with me?
等等 你他妈的在平安夜和我分手？
Wait, you're breakin' up with me on Christmas Eve?
瑟艾拉 你他妈的和我开玩笑吧？
Sheila, you have got to be fuckin' kidding me!
瑟艾拉
Sheila!
妈的 真他妈的爽
Well, that's just great.
妈的
God!
我早就知道
I knew it!
你不是真心的
You're not real.
你一直就不是真心的
You were never real.
你懂那种失望的感觉么
You know what that kind of disappointment
为人付出的感觉么？
can do to somebody?
你明白那会
Do you have any idea
让你下地狱的吗？
how that can fuck with your mind?
下地狱吧 去死吧你
Fuck with your mind! Fuck with your mind!
你他妈的 去你妈的
你妹你妹夫你全家的
Fuck with your mind!
恰吉又出问题了
Chucky is broke again.
这是血淋淋的谋杀
This is bloody ridiculous.
停 停 停
Cut! Cut! Cut!
停止造雪
Kill the snow.
滚开
Get off me.
汤尼 刚才咋回事？
Tony, what was that?
抱歉 那只是 只是 .
I'm sorry, it's… it's…
这太业余了 老子不干了
This is unprofessional, and I can't work like this!
不 杰森 很抱歉 杰森 等等
No, Jason, I'm sorry.No, Jason. Please wait.
我们现处好莱坞场地 现场正拍摄
We're here in Hollywood, where production is underway
一部新恐怖大片《内心中恰吉》
on the new horror flick, Chucky Goes Psycho.
影片讲述了恰吉和蒂凡尼的都市传奇
The film tells the urban legend of Chucky and Tiffany,
两个娃娃充当连环杀手
two dolls supposedly possessed by serial killers.
两个娃娃在戏里出现意外
The dolls were found at the scene
险酿真实谋杀
of a string of real-life murders
直至今日问题还没有解决
which remain unsolved to this day.
嘿 伙计们 我想 呃 蒂凡尼的左臂又松了
Hey, you guys, I think, uh, Tiffany's left arm is loose again.
是的 呃 我在找詹妮弗
Yeah, uh, I'm looking for Jennifer.
有人知道詹妮弗去哪了么？
Does anyone have a 20 on Jennifer?
去餐车里看看
Check the catering truck.
呃
Mmm.
詹妮弗 我给你找了种减肥饮料
Jennifer.I got you a Skinny Quick.
哦 嗯
Oh, uh…
泰莉小姐 我们都在等你上镜呢
Miss Tilly, we're ready for you on set.
詹妮弗 我可真是服了你
Jennifer, I am so proud of you.
为什么？
For what?
你还能照喝不误
For sticking to your diet.
噢 谢谢
Oh, thank you.
今天有啥新闻？
What's going on in the world today?
茱莉亚·罗伯特的下部片酬达到了2500万
Julia Roberts is getting$25 million for her next film.
又是茱莉亚·罗伯特
Julia Roberts.
这个茱莉亚·罗伯特我都听烦了
I'm so tired of hearing about Julia Roberts.
你知道 艾伦·布劳克伟什应该让我来演
You know, I should have played Erin Brockovich.
我不用加厚胸罩就能演好
I could have done it without a Wonderbra.
茱莉亚抢了我的那部分戏
Julia stole that part right out from under me.
然后你知道 她怎么做的么？
And you know how she did it?
她和导演睡觉了
She slept with the director.
一定是
That's what I think.
詹妮弗 你知道不是那么回事的
Jennifer, you know that's not true.
那我怎么就没有被分到好角色呢？
How come I don't ever get any of the good roles anymore?
那怎么就没人重视我呢？
How come nobody takes me seriously?
奶子很漂亮
Nice tits.
谢谢
Thank you.
看看我 我才是应该被奥斯卡提名的人
Look at me. I'm an Oscar nominee, for Christ's sake.
现在 我却和一个娃娃搞在了一起
Now I'm fucking a puppet.
没有粉丝邮箱 没有粉丝团 没有一举成名作
I've got no fan mail, no paparazzi, no stalkers.
听着 一定会有适合我的角色的
Well, there must be something I'm right for?
让我瞧瞧
Let's see.
呃 哦
Uh… Oh.
流行音乐巨星「红男」转行做了导演
Hip-hop superstar turned director, Red man,
正在寻找合适的女主角
is still looking for the right actress
去扮演圣经里的女权领导者
to take the female lead in his upcoming Bible epic.
哇喔 听起来不错 扮演谁？
Well, that sounds good. What's the role?
圣母玛利亚
The Virgin Mary.
有啥好笑的？
What's so funny?
没啥
Nothing.
这多好
It's perfect.
这正是让我展现自己的机会
It's just what I need to reinvent myself.
圣母玛利亚
The Virgin Mary.
我一直都喜欢她身着长袍
I always loved the way she wore robes
长发披肩的样子 就像这样
and her hair off her face, kind of like this.
琼 琼 去给莫特力打电话
Joan, Joan, get Morty on the phone
告诉他我想和「红男」见面
and tell him I need to take a meeting with this Redman.
现在就去
Right away.
好的
Okay.
好莱坞快讯
That's a wrap for Access Hollywood.
来自好莱坞片场 在这 就像你看到的
Reporting from Hollywood, where, as you can see,
恰吉和蒂凡尼活的好好的
Chucky and Tiffany are alive and well.
电影将在下个万圣节上映
You can catch their movie in theaters next Halloween.
谢谢 恰吉
Thank you, Chucky.
真想干你们
Fuck you very much.
（日本制造）
我现在总算是知道了
I'm no orphan after all!
那么
Well,
你昨晚表现糟透了
you were shit last night.
你应该表现得更惊恐一些
You are going to have to be more scary.
惊恐？
Scary?
嗯哼
U h-huh.
试试这个 来吧 好吧？
Let's rehearse, shall we, all right?
哦
Oh.
你好
Hello.
听着 你要学着点
Look, you got to learn
会学习使用杀手的本性 哥们
to tap into your killer instincts, mate,
把这本性变成你的本能
give in to your natural impulses.
否则我就会 呃
Or else I'm going to have to, uh,
烧掉你
fire you.
嘿
Hey!
回来
Come here!
赶紧回来
快回来
Come here!
「玛利亚 你真是一尘不染的纯洁圣女」
"Mary, you are truly a vision of unsullied innocence,
「在所有的女人中独一无二」
"unique among all women,
「就像无暇的白雪一样圣洁」
"as pure as the virgin snow"
「但是我想知道 什么事正在困扰你」
"But I ask, what is troubling you?"
「约瑟夫 我的夫君啊 真是奇迹」
"Joseph, husband, there has been a miracle.
「我就站在你的面前 向你宣布」
"As I stand before you, I must tell you
「我怀孕了」
'1 am with child."
「但是 玛利亚 这怎么可能？」
"But, Mary, how could this be?
「遵循上帝的旨意」
"In accordance with God's wishes,
「我们从来没有像凡人夫妻那样睡过」
"we have never lain together as man and wife."
「是的 一点没错」
"Yes, it is true.
「现在我祈求你相信我所说的」
"And I beg you that you believe me when I tell you
「我从来没和其他男人睡过」
'1 have never lain with any man at all.
「你相信我么 约瑟夫？相信么？」
"Do you believe me, Joseph? Do you?"
相信吗？
Do you?
是的 是的 我相信
Yes. Yes, I do.
呃 你很出色 棒极了
Uh, you were great. You were super.
谢谢 谢谢你 「红男」先生
Thank you, thank you, Mr. Man.
哦 我能叫你「红哥」么？
Oh, can I call you Red?
听着 我还能表演出各种不同的演技方法
Listen, there's a whole lot of different ways I could do it.
不仅仅是你刚才看到的
Not just the way you saw.
我能演的 我能演的快一点 或慢一点
I could do it, I could do it faster, slower.
我能 我甚至能表演说唱
I could… I could do it as a rap.
呃 不 不 不
Uh, no, no, no, no.
你已经给我看了一种风格
You already showed me a side of the character
这种风格我以前从未见过
that, uh, I've never seen before.
哦 谢谢
Oh, thank you.
但是 我还是要选择我的第一人选
But I think I'm going to have to go with my first choice.
非常感谢你能来试镜
Thanks for comm1 by anyway.
我是说 我是你的超级脑残粉
I mean, really, I'm a huge, huge fan.
我真的很想有一天能和你共事 我会给你打电话 .
I really want to work with you one day.We should call…
呃 不好意思 冒昧的问一下
Urn, excuse rne, I hope you don't rnind rny asking,
谁是你的第一人选？
but who is your first choice?
茱莉亚·罗伯特
Julia Roberts.
不管怎样 多谢赏光
But thanks for comm1 by, anyway.
呃 听着 听着 「红哥哥」
Urn, listen, listen, Red.
呃 我特别想饰演这个角色
Urn, I've been giving a lot of thought to this project,
关于这个角色
and I have a lot of interesting ideas
我还有一些比较有趣的构思
about the character.
然后我认为
And I was thinkin' maybe
或许我们应该到一个私密的地方讨论讨论
you would like to discuss it in a more intimate setting.
就我们两个
Just the two of us.
哦 哦 好吧
Oh. Oh, well,
我刚才不知道你对这角色这么有激情
I didn't know you were that passionate about the role.
哦 是的 我很有激情
Oh, yes, I'm very passionate.
嗯
Mmm.
那么 就来我家吧？
So, shall we say my place?
八点怎么样？
8:00?
对不起 先生
Pardon me, sir.
哦 天啊
Oh. Oh.
呃 对不起
Uh, sorry.
对不起 先生
Sorry, sir.
别介意
Don't mind me.
冒昧了
Excuse me.
哦 天啊
Oh, dear.
哦 天啊 我的天啊
Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
老妈？
Mom?
老爸？
Dad?
我一生都在梦想着这一刻
I've dreamed of this moment all my life.
我知道这一刻一定让人很震惊
I know this must come as quite a shock.
我们彼此都需要一个适应过程
It's going to be an adjustment for all of us.
看 我现在还留着你们留给我的项链
Look, I still have the necklace you left me.
我一直都想知道 这些话是什么意思？
I've always wanted to know, what do these words mean?
是我们的家族铭言么？
Is it our family motto?
求你们说话啊
Please say something.
是因为我很丑吗？是吗？
It's because of the way I look, isn't it?
看在上帝的份上 醒醒吧
For pity's sake, please wake up.
啊
Huh
「醒醒」？
"Wake up"?
[咒语]
「苏醒吧」
"Awake"
蒂凡尼？
Tiff?
恰吉？
Chucky?
你他妈的是谁？
Who the hell are you?
丑脸
Shitface.
那 这算他妈的什么鸟名字？
Now, what kind of a name is that?
你老妈和老爸呢？
Where are your mother and father?
看你那张脸 我猜他们都没脸见人
Judging from that face, my guess is they're hidin'.
闭嘴 混蛋
Shut up, you asshole.
好吧 看看吧 这孩子要多丑有多丑
Well, come on. It looks like the kid hell off the ugly tree
他们全家一定也都这么丑
and hit every branch on the way down.
我是说 你该为你的父母感到自卑
I mean, you got to feel bad for the parents.
我猜他们也一定长这个丑样
I wonder what they must look like.
哇喔
Whoa.
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
（你们好 妈妈爸爸）
纳尼？不
What? No.
我们 呃 你没有 我们没有
We, uh…You didn't… We didn't…
小心肝 快来妈妈这
Sweetface, come to Mommy.
这 .这怎么回事？
What's… What's going on?
我们在哪？
Where are we?
在好莱坞
In Hollywood.
我在电视上看到你们了
I saw you on the telly.
恰吉 恰吉 醒醒
Chucky, Chucky, wake up.
看看我们 我们成名了
Look at us. We've had makeovers.
我们是影星了
We're movie stars.
妈的 开启芭芘模式
Shit. Barbie mode.
不 他们就是娃娃
No, they're puppets.
他们不会说话 也不会走路
They don't walk and talk by themselves.
听着 想要修好他们
Listen, if you want them to work,
我就得拆了他们
I'm going to have to take them apart.
妈妈病了么？
Is Mommy ill?
道具师认为是病了
The courts thought so.
抬起头来
Heads up!
他们真的是疯了
They're stark raving mad!
嘿 你尿裤子了
Hey, you're pissin'your pants.
恰吉 她只是被吓到了而已
Chucky, she just had an accident.
你是说「他」被吓到了？
You mean, "he" had an accident.
别盯着我看
Don't look at me.
看吧 我说过她是女孩的吧？
See, what did I tell you?
一个漂亮的小丫头
A beautiful little girl.
什么？你瞎了？是个小男孩
What? Are you blind? That's my boy.
是的
Yeah.
只是小鸡鸡还没发育好
He just hasn't had his growth spurt, yet.
儿子 别担心
Don't worry about it, Son.
你发育的有点晚 就是这样
You're a late bloomer, that's all.
现在关键是你得有个真正的名字了
And it's high time that you had a real name.
让我想想
Let's see.
我认为我们就叫你
I think I'm going to call you
格林
Glen.
格林？
Glen?
女孩儿起这名字哪行？
What kind of a name is that for a girl?
亲爱的 别听他的 从现在开始 你的名字就是
Don't listen to him, honey. From now on, your name is
格琳达
Glenda.
快跑 格琳达
Run, Glenda.
天啊 真够乱的
Jeez, what a mess.
呃
Ugh.
在这了 巧克力先生
There you are, Mr. Goodbar.
詹妮弗·泰莉
Jennifer Tilly.
你好
Hello.
嘿
Hey.
哦 天啊 你可真逼真
Oh, my God. You look so real.
真够逼真的
You look so real.
你比我前男友还要可爱
You are cuter than my last boyfriend.
我想我们真是可爱的一对
I think we make a lovely couple.
詹妮弗 泰莉小姐 你和他有什么过节么？
Jennifer. Miss Tilly, were you having an affair with him?
我不懂你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我是皮特 名人访谈栏目组
Pete Peters, Celebrities Revealed.
詹妮弗 你刚才看到什么了？
Jennifer, what did you see?
操 难道你让我给你画下来？
What, you want me to draw you a picture?
你能画么？
Would you?
谁递过来一张纸
Somebody give her a piece of paper.
听着 我不会给你画出来的 好不？
Look, I'm not gonna draw you a picture, okay?
哦 别这么沮丧
Oh, don't feel bad.
你是一个演员 不是艺术家
You're an actress not an artist.
当你看到尸体的时候你在干什么？
What were you doin' when you sawthe body?
无可奉告
No comment.
詹妮弗 我爱你
Jennifer, I love you.
你和「红男」真的谈过话么？
Is it true that you and Redman are in talks
关于出演他的新片子的事？
about you starring in his new movie?
是的 事实上 是这样的 我已经
Yes. As a matter of fact, that is true. I have…
能签个名么？
Can I have your autograph?
当然 可以
Okay, sure.
嘿 等等 你们忘记脑袋了
Hey, hold on, you forgot the head.
对不起 让一让 借过一下
Excuse me. Excuse me. Excuse me.
詹妮弗 你实际年龄多大？
Jennifer, how old are you really?
该死的狗仔队
Paparazzi scumbag!
你是哪一年出生的？
What year were you born?
给我们一个确切的日期
Give us the exact date.
我要和你一起坐在前面
I want to sit up front with you.
好的
Sure.
你在逃避什么？
What are you hiding?
嘿 你还好么？
Hey, you okay?
是的 现在非常好
Yeah, I am now.
我们驰骋在林荫路上
* We're on the boulevard *
在我车里尽情的兜着风
* We're cruisin' in my car *
看着人们转身向我们聚焦
* See all the fellows turn to look and see *
那么 你们是一对忍者杀手？
So, are you a pair of ninja assassins?
啊？
Huh?
你们为日本黑帮卖命杀人？
Are you hit men for the yakuza?
我们不是日本人
We're not from Japan.
我们是新泽西人
We're from Jersey.
想想吧 詹妮弗·泰莉在电影里扮演我
Just think, Jennifer Tilly is playing me in a movie.
那是多么完美的演绎
It's absolutely perfect casting.
但是那只是配音
But that voice!
我知道 他的声线犹如天使般动人
I know, she sounds just like an angel.
现在 我全都计划好了
Now, I've got it all figured out.
我把我的灵魂化身为詹妮弗
I'm going to transfer my soul into Jennifer
你把你的灵魂化身为「红男」
and you're going to transfer your soul into Redman.
这主意真不错
I'm down with that.
我们借他们的身体玩一次就好了
We'll ditch these plastic bodies once and for all,
然后我们将成为好莱坞最红的一对
and we'll be Hollywood's hottest couple.
那我呢？
What about me?
别担心 格琳达
Don't worry, Glenda.
我也帮你计划好了
I've got that figured out, too.
你长大后会真的成为一个女孩
You're going to be a real live girl.
男孩
Boy.
怎么做？
How?
那么 我不能再怀孕了 我一直都这么说
Well, I'm not getting pregnant again, I'll tell you that much.
我妈妈以前一直告诉我
My mother always told me,
说一次是祝福 说两次是诅咒
Once is a blessing. Twice is a curse.!!
嗯 难怪你妹妹会那样
Well, that would explain your sister.
真心爱你的人只有妈妈一个
The only sensible option is a surrogate mother.
嘿
Hey.
詹妮弗 我有一些重要的事
Jennifer, I have something important…
是的 等会 宝贝
Yeah, hold on a second, sweetheart.
喂 哪位？
Hello?
你丫在干嘛呢？
What are you doing?
我在忙呢
I'm busy.
我真的很充实 你知道的
I do have a life, you know.
看看新闻吧
Turn on the news.
你们有过冲突么？
Were you having an affair?
一位女演员发现了被害人的尸体
The actress discovered the victim's body.
然而 警方也无法定论
As of yet, there is no official confirmation
泰莉小姐是否就是疑犯
as to whether or not Miss Tilly is a suspect.
天啊
Jesus!
你能相信这个么？
Can you believe this?
你还好么？
Are you okay?
会好起来的
I've had better days.
呃 听着 琼 帮我做点事
Urn, listen, Joan, I need you to do sornething for rne.
帮我买瓶香槟
I need you to get rne a bottle of charnpagne
然后带到我家去
and bring it by my house.
干什么用？
What for?
嗯
Well,
今晚有个约会
I've got a big night tonight.
今晚？
Tonight?
和谁？
With who?
「红男」
Redman.
詹妮弗 你要干什么？
Jennifer, what are you up to?
多谢了 琼
Thank you, Joan.
嘿 别这样 斯坦 生意而已嘛
Oh, come on, Stan, it's just business.
午夜之前他就会走的
He'll be out of there by midnight.
哦 天啊 她真是个荡妇
Oh, my God, she's a complete slut.
晚安 格琳达 睡个好觉
Nighty-night, Glenda. Sleep tight.
把灯开着
Leave it on.
哦 宝贝 这没什么好害怕的
Oh, sweetie, there's nothing to be scared of.
你爸爸和我会一直在这的
Your daddy and I will be right here.
你们为什么要杀人？
Why do you kill people?
什么？
Excuse me?
你们为什么杀人？
Why do you kill?
习惯而已 真的 能让我们放松起来
It's a hobby, really. It helps us relax.
我也会成为一名杀手么？
Am I going to be a killer?
当然 这已经是家族传统了
Of course. It's been a family tradition for generations.
但是 暴力是不好的 不是吗？
But violence is bad, isn't it?
电视上是这么说的
They said so on TV.
不是「暴力」
Not "violence."
「小提琴」 小提琴是不好的
"Violins." Violins are bad.
那个该死的音乐声会毁了整个国家
That screeching music's gonna ruin the goddamn country.
恰吉 格琳达是对的
Chucky, Glenda's right.
是该我们收手的时候了
It's time we owned up to it.
我们杀人是错误的
We have a problem with killing.
我觉得杀人没什么「错误」
I don't have "a problem" with killing.
过去和现在 我都喜欢杀人
I like a little killing now and then.
那又有什么问题呢？
What's wrong with that?
杀人就像毒品一样会让人成瘾
Killing is an addiction, like any other drug.
但是我们身为父母
But we're parents now.
就必须要做出好榜样
We have to set a good example.
嘿 恰吉 我们收手吧 就现在
Oh, let's quit, Chucky, right now.
戒掉它吧
Cold turkey.
你一定是和我开玩笑
You have got to be kidding.
答应我 恰吉 别再杀人了
Promise me, Chucky, no more killing.
不
No.
- 恰吉 - 不 不
- Chucky? - No, no.
- 不在杀人了 - 不 不
- No more killing. - No, no.
- 我们别在杀人了 - 不 不
- We can't do it anymore. - No, no.
永远都不答应
A thousand times no.
我们得为未来打算了 我们有孩子了
We have the future to think of. We have a child!
好吧
Fine!
好吧 行了 我答应你
All right, already. I promise.
谢谢你 小芭比
Thank you, doll baby.
你真贴心
You're a sweetheart.
现在我们真的是完美的一家子
Now we really will be the perfect family.
你刚才听到了啥了么？
Did you hear that?
或许你该忘了那个导演
Maybe you should forget the director
然后去和终结者上床
and fuck the Terminator instead.
怎样 我看起来怎么样？
So, how do I look?
无所谓
Never mind.
詹妮弗 这会作贱你自己的
Jennifer, this is beneath you.
想想你在做什么吧
Think about what you're doing.
人们会说些什么？
What are people gonna say?
管他们怎么说？
Who cares what people say?
但是你不认为这有多低俗么？
But don't you see how evil this is?
我不想听这个
I don't wanna hear it.
你这是在出卖你自己
You're prostituting yourself
然后换取圣母玛利亚的角色
so you can play the Virgin Mary.
琼 我不想听这个
Joan, I don't wanna hear it.
哦 这太低俗了
Oh, this is so evil.
- 你会下地狱的 - 不会
- You're going to hell. - No.
在恐怖明星秀节目里
Hell would be ending up on Celebrity Fear Factor
和安娜·史密斯一起比赛吃蚯蚓才叫地狱呢
in a worm-eating contest with Anna Nicole Smith.
哪回你赢过
Which you'd win.
他来了
He's here.
你从后面走
Let yourself out the back.
还有你等会走的时候
And while you're at it,
把钥匙留在柜台上
why don't you leave your key on the counter?
你说什么？
What are you saying?
好吧 你认为我很恶心
Well, you think I'm so disgusting.
你认为我会下地狱
You think I'm going to hell.
我只不过是迫于生计而已 琼
I'm only trying to survive here, Joan.
上帝知道我曾经想过把你也拉下水
God knows I wouldn't want to drag you down with me.
我是说你现在被炒了
I'm saying you're fired.
干死他们
* Cut 'em up *
我要狂爆你的菊
* I'm gonna hit that ass *
现在 在人工授精的时候 时机最为重要
Now, in artificial insemination, timing is everything.
所以你得抓紧了
So you'll have to hurry.
对你来说这不是问题
That shouldn't be a problem for you.
是的 不要让他把那家伙塞进她的裤裆里
Yeah, yeah, just don't let that player get into her pants.
在我们没有完成灵魂互换之前
I don't want him touching my woman
我不想有人碰我的女人
till I'm him and you're her.
好的
Right.
嘿
Hey.
现在你得帮帮忙来点刺激的
Aren't you going to give me a hand here?
嗯
Mmm.
太高了
Too tall.
嘿 女同们
Hey, Iezbos.
就是他了
Done her.
来吧
Here we go.
来老爸这里
Come to papa.
干杯
Cheers.
你知道吗 当我说我是你的粉丝时 我不是骗你的
You know, I wasn't bulishittin'when I told you I was a fan.
哦 嘴巴真甜 「红哥哥」
Oh, That's so sweet, Redman.
你最喜欢我的哪部片子？
Which of my films is your favorite?
你和一个妞搞女同的那部
That movie when you and that chick was makin' out.
哦 《惊世狂花》 大家都喜欢那部
Oh, Bound. Everybody likes that one.
你和她还有联系么？
You still in touch with homegirl?
- 吉娜？ - 是的
- Gina? - Yeah.
哦 是的 我们现在时朋友
Oh, yeah, sure, we're friends.
哇喔 很亲昵的朋友
Wow. Close friends.
哇喔
Whoa.
非常亲昵
Very close friends.
或许 我们三个
Maybe, the three of us
可以找时间一起出去玩玩
could hang out together some time.
你知道 我真的是超喜欢那样的
You know, I would really like that a lot.
好吧 我看能不能约她出来
Okay. I'll see if I can make it happen.
喝光他 宝贝
Bottoms up, baby.
干杯
Skol.
红哥哥 呃
Redman, urn,
我想知道要怎么样
I was wondering what's it gonna take
才能让我去扮演圣母玛利亚
to make you see me as a virgin.
好吧 你来告诉我
Well, you tell me.
打飞机的小矮子？
A masturbating midget?
拍到你了 小矮子
Get it, mini-meat.
哇喔
Whoa.
哦 天啊 上帝保佑这些小矮子
Oh, sweet Jesus, God bless the little people.
我想我不能这样
I don't know if I can do this.
为什么不行？
Why not?
大家都会怎么说？
What will people say?
去他妈的「大家会怎么说」
Man, fuck what people say.
知道我怎么说吗 命中注定 真的 宝贝
Know what I'm saying? This was meant to be, baby, for real.
知道我怎么知道的么？
Know how I know?
因为上帝告诉我的
Because the man upstairs told me so.
真的吗？
Really?
当然 是的
Hell, yeah.
听着 梅尔·吉布森不是唯一的一个
Look, Mel Gibson ain't the only one
在好莱坞和上帝谈过话的人
God's been talkin' to in Hollywood.
上帝私下里告诉我 你就是我的圣母玛利亚
And He personally told me that you was my Virgin.
好吧 我想
Well, I guess…
怎么个事？
What the hell?
蠢猪
Pig.
还有你
And you…
你该为你自己而感到羞耻
You should be ashamed of yourself.
你的自尊哪去了？
Where's your self-respect?
你知道我妈妈以前都怎么描述小贱货的么？
You know what my mother used to say about dirty girls?
「闻其骚」
She said, "you can always smell it
「即知其有多淫」
"on girls who sell it."
呃 顺便问一下 泰莉小姐 能给签个名么？
Urn, by the way, Miss Tilly, can I have your autograph?
我是你的超级粉丝
I'rn a big fan.
我该怎么处理这个东西呢？
What am I supposed to do with this?
现在 泰莉小姐 我知道你现在吓懵了
Now, Miss Tilly, I know you're frightened.
甚至在怀疑自己
You're probably even wondering
是否完全的清醒
if you've gone completely insane.
不过我答应你 明日你醒过来
But I promise you, tomorrow you're going to wake up,
所有的这些都只不过是一场噩梦而已
and this will all seem just like a bad dream.
在此期间 我们可以来软的
In the meantime, we can do this the easy way
或者来硬的
or the hard way.
这都取决于你
It's really up to you.
怪不得她总是这么不走运
No wonder her career's in trouble.
检查一下 蒂凡尼
Check it out, Tiff.
看看他的脚有多大
Look at the size of his feet.
你懂我在说什么
You know what they say.
操 她太胖了
Fuck, she's fat.
我真不敢相信 她都没有怀过孕
I can't believe it. She's not even pregnant yet.
该死的狗仔队
Paparazzi scumbag.
呃 看来你一切尽在掌握之中
Uh, looks like you've got everything under control.
一切就交给你了
I'll just leave you to it.
好完美的阴道啊
Motherhood is so beautiful.
不
No.
不要啊
不要
No.
对不起 开个玩笑而已
Sorry, just messin' with you.
现在几点了
What time is it?
该起床打扮了
Time to get dressed.
我们俩来一个男人之夜 就你和我
We are going to have our own boys'night out, just you and me.
这听起来怎么样？
How does that sound?
我们要去哪？
Where are we going?
打猎
Hunting.
我什么也看不到
I can't see anything.
或许你应该开慢点
Maybe we should slow down?
不 你做的很好
No! You're doing great.
贱货养的
Son of a bitch!
来啊 混蛋
Up yours, asshole!
怎么了？
What?
不是说你 儿子 快 加速
Not you, Son. Come on, floor it!
哇喔 我又干了一次
Wow! I did it again.
我的天啊
Jesus Christ!
不要
No!
好儿子
Attaboy!
不 我没有
No, I didn't…
我想你可能还没准备好
And I thought you weren't ready.
孩子 你真是他妈的天生杀手
Kid, you're a fuckin' natural!
但是他 他是自己弄倒的架子
But he… he hit the shelf.
别怕你妈妈
And don't worry about your mother.
这是我们之间的小秘密
It will be our little secret.
说「奶酪」
Say "cheese."
早上好
Good morning.
哦 嘿
Oh. Hi.
昨晚我们俩一定非常疯狂
We must have really got wired last night.
是的
Yeah.
红哥哥 你记得吗？
Redman, did we…
你记不 记不住了？
You don't… You don't remember?
恩 一片模糊
No. It's all a blur.
你能记住么？
What about you?
我记得你好像尖叫了几次
I kind of remember you screamin' a lot.
哦 是 我好像也想起来了
Oh, yeah, I seem to remember that, too.
你知道吗 我隐约听到有其他女人的声音
You know, I tend to have that effect on women.
真的吗？
Really?
是的
Yeah.
等等 我记起来了
Wait, I do remember
我做了个奇怪的梦
I had the strangest dream.
梦见我的守护天使来到我的身边
I dreamt my guardian angel came to me.
她拥有我听过的最甜美的嗓音
She had the sweetest voice I have ever heard.
她告诉我要学会自重
She told me to respect myself.
然后她向我要了签名
And then she asked for my autograph.
来看看
Let's see.
第一步 承认自己已经上瘾
Admit I have an addiction.
好的 无所谓了
Okay, check.
第二步：
"Step Number Two:
提高自己的自信心
"Give myself over to a higher power."
管他呢
Whatever.
哦 这一步
Oh. Here we go.
第九步
"Step Number Nine:
想要治愈自己的瘾好
"The recovering addict must make amends
就要向任何被自己伤害的人道歉
"to anyone he or she has harmed."
嗯
Hmm.
喂 哪位？
Hello?
早上好
Good morning.
是茹斯·贝利女士么？
Is this Ruth Bailey?
是我
Speaking.
罗伯特·贝利的遗孀？
The widow of Robert Bailey?
是的 你是谁？
Yes. Who is this?
贝利夫人 我的名字叫蒂凡尼·蕾
Mrs. Bailey, my name is Tiffany Ray.
呃 你不认识我
Urn, you don't know me,
但是在几年前 我杀了你的丈夫
but a few years ago, I killed your husband.
我致以真诚的歉意
And I am so very, very sorry.
搞什么呢 恶作剧玩笑？
What is this, some kind of sick joke?
哦 不 我真的是认真的
Oh, no, I'm completely serious.
但是你要知道 我现在正在忏悔呢
But I want you to know I'm in recovery now
然后我会试图把一切都忘掉
and I have put all of that behind me.
我不知道你是谁
I don't know who you are…
谢谢 贝利夫人
Thank you, Mrs. Bailey.
祝你愉快
Have a nice day.
我感觉好多了
I feel better already.
早上好 斯坦
Morning, Stan.
嘿 你不是有重要的事
Hey, wasn't there something important
要和我说么？
you wanted to tell me?
好吧 嗯
Well, uh,
事情就是 詹妮弗
the thing is, Jennifer…
不好意思
I'm sorry.
我不知道我怎么回事
I don't know what's gotten into me.
呃 那么你想说的是
Urn, so you were saying…
算了吧
Forget it.
好吧
Okay.
现在 让我们想想
Now, let's see.
我们今天要干什么
What should we do today?
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
「红哥哥」 我说我怀孕了
Red man, I said I'm pregnant.
恭喜啊
Congratulations.
孩子他爹是谁？
Who is the baby's daddy?
别盯着我看
Don't even look at me.
好吧 最近为了事业发展
Well, I haven't slept with anyone else
我没和其他人睡过
to advance my career lately.
你可真逗
Who are you kidding
是真的 红男 听着
It's true, Red man. Look,
我知道我看上去像个荡妇
I know I come off all slutty,
但是那是 那是 在我看来 那只是…
but that's…that's…for my image. It's just…
你知道大家都怎么看待我么？
Do you think anyone would cast me?
在这个肮脏的交际圈里
In these sexpot roles,
他们知道我一年都没有做过爱么？
if they knew I hadn't been laid in a year?
我甚至都没有和我的司机做过
I haven't even slept with my driver yet
我想他真的非常喜欢我
and I think he really likes me.
嘿 这可真他妈的感人
Hey, that's all very touchin' and shit.
但是我告诉你 肯定不可能是我
But I'm telling you, it can't be me.
为什么？
Why not?
我一到好莱坞就坐了输精管结扎术
I had a vasectomy as soon as I got to Hollywood.
我可不是傻子
I ain't no idiot.
好吧 那么 那就不可能了 我
Well, then, that's impossible. I…
嘿 詹妮弗
Hey, Jennifer,
我不想伤你的心
I hate to break itto you.
但是如果你怀孕了 就别想拍我的戏了
But I can't hire you if you're pregnant.
那太可笑了
That is ridiculous.
演员是个孕妇
The character is pregnant.
是的 我知道
Yeah, I know,
但是我非常想要个特别的圣母玛利亚
but I have a very specific vision of Mary.
我该怎么说？
And what can I say?
她一定会大红大紫
She gots to be hot.
蠢猪
That pig!
戒毒康复热线
Recovery Hotline.
你好 我正在戒毒康复期
Yes, I'm in recovery.
然而我现在很担心我就要犯错误了
And I'm afraid I'm going to have a slip.
能出来见见面么？
Can you get to a meeting?
不 这个倒没必要
No, it's really not an option.
我只不过是让大家都吓到了
I just freak everybody out.
不要太这么自责
Don't be so hard on yourself.
我们又不会给你判刑
We're not here to judge you.
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
蒂凡尼
Tiffany.
听着 蒂凡尼
Listen to me, Tiffany.
我很清楚你该怎么做
I know exactly what you are going through.
你知道？
You do?
是的 我…我知道
Yes, I… I do.
老实说 我要和你分享一个小秘密
In fact, I'm gonna let you in on a little secret.
就在上周 我也犯错误了
Just last week, I had a slip.
真的吗？
Really?
是的
Yes.
相信我 我也并非完人
And believe you me, it was not pretty.
从来就没有完美的人 是吧？
It never is, is it?
事实上 我花了三个小时才收拾干净
In fact, it took me 3 hours just to clean up the mess.
哦 天啊 别这么提醒我
Oh, God, don't remind me.
但是我并没有对此而感到内疚
But I'm not beating myself up over it.
你知道为什么吗 蒂凡尼？
You know why, Tiffany?
为什么？
Why?
因为冰冻三尺非一日之寒
Because Rome wasn't built in a day.
你是对的
You're right.
说的太对了
You are absolutely right.
喂？是我
Hello? Speaking.
好吧 你是谁？
Well, who's this?
是我 我知道
All right, I know.
我知道你是谁
I understand who you are.
我就是不知道你是怎么搞到我的电话号码的
I just don't know how you got my phone number.
因为这是私人专线 非公开性的号码
Because it is a private, unlisted phone number.
彼得·皮特？
Pete Peters?
是的 我昨天见过他
Yeah, I saw him yesterday.
不 我和他没有任何关系
No, I don't have any relationship with him.
他就是个破狗仔
He is a firking paparazzi
一个总想给我拍照的家伙
that is trying to get pictures of me
偷拍的或者正式的
in compromising positions.
是的 我现在和「红男」在一起
Yeah, I'm with Redman.
「红男」 他是个导演
Redman, he's a director.
哦 是 他也是个说唱歌手
Oh, yeah. Well, he's a rapper, too.
他是说唱歌手兼导演 行了吧？
He is a rapper-director, okay?
转行了
He's a hyphenate.
再见
Bye-bye.
詹妮弗
Jennifer…
等一下 我在打电话呢
Do you mind? I'm on the phone.
又有一起凶杀案了
There's been another murder.
什么？不 我告诉过你我当时在哪
What? No, I told you where I was.
我一整晚都和「红男」在一起
I was right here all night with Redman.
什么？我不明白
What? I don't…
你现在别告诉我 我是嫌疑犯？
You're not telling me I'm a suspect?
好吧 我挂了
All right, I'll be fine.
我马上就去
I'm on my way.
我马上要出去
I'm leaving.
你自己回去吧
You can let yourself out.
顺带一句 「红男」你去死吧
By the way, Redman, drop dead.
哦 格琳达
Oh, Glenda.
格琳达 亲爱的 一切都会没事的
Glenda, honey. Everything is okay.
只是犯了一个小错误而已
It was just a little slip.
没有必要和你老爸说
There's no need to tell your daddy.
保住我们之间的小秘密 好不？
It will be our little secret, okay?
好不？嘘
Okay? Shh.
对于圣昆丁监狱来说 今天是个大日子
It's D-day here at San Quentin.
一个从来都不敢想的人来到了这个地方
Who would have thought it would ever come to this?
他们今天上午会收监玛莎·斯蒂沃特
They're executing Martha Stewart this morning.
我可受不了那九个月的屎生活
I don't think I can take nine months of this shit.
傻恰吉
Silly Chucky.
这是巫术怀孕
It is a voodoo pregnancy.
会很快的
It's accelerated.
有多快？
How accelerated?
大家好 欢迎收听FM102.7兆赫
It is I 02.7, KIIS FM,
洛杉矶第一音乐台
LA's number one hit music station.
瑞安·西克莱斯特在此做早间播报
Ryan Seacrest in the morning.
艾伦 我可不知道我能否吃得消这个
Ellen K., I don't know if I can take it.
这路上是什么东西？
What's on the way?
洛杉矶 好莱坞天气非常糟糕
We have bad weather on the way in LA, Hollywood,
周围附近区域也是
and surrounding area.
现在 我们都不太习惯坏天气
Now, we're not used to bad weather.
是我 我们很不习惯
No, we're not.
我不太确定这会不会影响到我一天的情绪
I'm not quite sure how that's going to affect my whole vibe.
你好 我是琼
This is Joan.
琼 琼 我
Joan. Joan, I'm…
我 我变胖了
I'm… I'm fat.
你一点都不胖
You're not fat.
不 我很胖 我 我变得超级胖了
No, I am fat. I'm… I'm huge!
敬爱的圣母啊 我怀孕了
For the love of Mary, I'm pregnant.
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
不 我应该听你的 琼
No, I should have listened to you, Joan.
你说这太低俗了 然后我会下地狱
You said it was evil and I was going to hell.
你是对的 现在上帝就在惩罚我
You're right, and now God is punishing me.
哦 天啊 是「红男」的孩子？
Oh, God. Is it Redman's?
不 当然不是红男的孩子
No, it's definitely not Redman's.
什么？你说什么？
What? What?
当然不是红男的孩子
It's definitely not Redman's.
那个混蛋
What an asshole.
你 你为什么那么说话？
W-What makes you say that?
说什么？
Say what?
「红男」是个混蛋
That Redman is an asshole.
- 我没有说过 - 是你刚说的
- I didn't say it - you did.
不 我没说过
No, I didn't.
那他就不是个混蛋？
So he's not an asshole?
是的 他是个混蛋
Yes, he is.
琼 能不能别在说了
Joan, will you please stop doing that?
说啥？
Doing what?
模仿我 我说话可不是那样
Imitating me. I do not sound like that.
哦 是的 你是对的 我确实在模仿
Oh, yes, you do. I do.
琼 你能不能闭嘴啊？
Joan, will you shut up?
我真的遇到麻烦了
There's something really wrong with me!
我怀孕了 我不明白
I'm pregnant. I don't…
詹妮弗 怎么回事？
Jennifer, what's wrong?
没事 没事 我很好
Nothing. Nothing, I'm fine.
我听到你尖叫了
I heard you scream.
我现在还能听到你尖叫
I can still hear you screaming!
哦 哦 我是说 那只是
Oh. Oh, I mean, it's just…
好吧 是电视台放的《惊世狂花》
Well, Bound is on cable.
吉娜·格尔森正在拿手指头捅我
Gina Gershon is fingering me.
我很喜欢这部电影 你呢？
I love this movie. Don't you?
詹妮弗
Jennifer.
是的 呃 那真是太有意思了
Yeah, uh-huh, that's really interesting,
但是我得挂了 拜
but I've got to go. Bye!
詹妮弗
Jennifer.
太紧了？
Too tight?
是的
Yes.
没这种事
Ain't no such thing.
你在干什么？停下来
What are you doing? Stop it.
这到底是他妈的怎么回事？
What the hell is going on in here?
她 呃 她要勾引我
She, urn, came on to rne.
救命啊 快来人救命啊
Help me!Somebody help me!
让她闭嘴 混蛋.
Shut her up, asshole.
救命啊 快来人救命啊
Help me! Somebody help me!
快来人救命啊
Somebody help me!
这他妈的是什么？
What the hell is this?
我们之前谈过的 恰吉
We had an agreement, Chucky.
我们决定 看在孩子的份上
We decided, for the sake of our child
再也不干这种事了
we weren't going to do this shit anymore!
不 是你决定了
No, you decided.
就像你决定了我们的儿子是个女儿一样
Just like you decided our son was a girl.
他是个女孩
He is a girl!
他是个男孩 妈的
He is a boy, God damn it!
然后他也是我曾经见过的
And he is the most promising killer
最有前途的杀手
I have ever seen.
你该看看当时的场景 蒂凡尼
You should have been there, Tiff.
你会为他而感到自豪的
You would have been so proud of him.
我想要个女孩
I want a girl!
我想要个男孩
I want a boy!
你们快把我弄崩溃了
You are tearing me apart!
想想我的感受好不好？
What about what I want?
什么？
What?
难道我的想法就毫无意义？
Doesn't what I want mean anything at all?
哦
Oh.
好吧 有点意思 说说吧
Okay, interesting. Tell us.
你是怎么想的 小心肝
What do you want, Sweetface?
我想我要成为一个男孩
I think I want to be a boy.
对的 看看你的脸色 女士
Yes! In your face, lady!
但是做一个女孩也是很不错的
But being a girl would be nice, too.
嗯…
Hmm…
好吧 此话怎讲？
Well, which is it?
我也不知道
I'm not sure.
有时感觉自己是个男孩
Sometimes I feel like a boy.
有时感觉自己又是个女孩
Sometimes I feel like a girl.
能否既是男孩又是女孩？
Can't I be both?
好吧 有的人…
Well, some people…
呃 没门
Uh-uh!No way!
但是有一件事我非常确定
But one thing I do know for sure.
我不想成为一名杀手
I don't want to be a killer.
格琳达 格林 管他呢
Glenda. Glen. Whatever.
我真为你感到自豪
I'm so proud of you.
无论发生什么
No matter what happens,
我们都会紧紧相依 一家亲
we'll deal with it together, as a family!
这真是 极好的
Okay, Okasan!
等一下
Wait a minute.
我不准你用什么狗屁感人12步疗法
I'm not going to let you poison our son's mind
来毒害我们儿子的思想
with your touchy-feely, 12-step bulishit.
如果你们两个不想再杀人了
If you two don't want to kill anymore,
那是你们的损失
that's your loss.
但是请以后不要对我指手画脚
But don't look down your noses at me.
我不以杀手为耻
I'm not ashamed to be a killer.
我却以此为荣
I'm proud of it.
这不是什么「上瘾」
It is not an addiction.
这是一种「选择」
It is a choice.
这也不是那些你能
And it is not something
轻而易举藏起来的东西
that you should have to hide in a closet!
哇哦
Whoa!
哦
Oh.
哦 天啊
Oh, dear.
哦 上帝啊
Oh, God.
好吧 好吧 好吧
Well, well, well.
看起来高尚圣洁女士
Looks like Miss High and Mighty
也不是如此圣洁和高尚
ain't so perfect after all.
犯了一个小错而已嘛
It was just a little slip.
罗马也不是一天建成的 你知道的
Rome wasn't built in a day, you know.
还有 这混蛋也真的该死
Besides, the fucker really had it coming.
好吧 那我的肉体躯壳怎么办？
Well, what about my body?
我会搞定的
I'll take care of it.
詹妮弗 我爱你 詹妮弗 我爱你
Jennifer, I love you. Jennifer, I love you.
我爱你
I love you.
你好 我是斯坦
This is Stan.
你好 我是詹妮弗
Hello, it's Jennifer.
斯坦 宝贝 我需要你的身体
Stan, baby, I need your body.
我马上就到
I'll be right there.
詹妮弗 如果我遭遇不测
Jennifer, if anything happens to me,
我想要你知道
I want you to know…
他们真是天造地设的一对
They really do make a cute couple,
你认为呢？
don't you think?
就像我老妈一直说的
It's like my mother always said…
够了
Christ!
你老妈说的够多的了 够了
Enough with your mother, already!
我20年前就已经杀了那个贱货
I killed that bitch 20 years ago
现在她仍然还没有闭嘴
and she still won't shut up.
好了 好了 不会太久的
There, there. It won't be long now.
詹妮弗
Jennifer!
谁在外面？
Who is it?
詹妮弗
Jennifer!
是那个碎嘴贱人 琼
It's that nosy bitch, Joan.
我去搞定她
I'll take care of her.
我不想让你
I wouldn't want you
毁掉你那牛逼闪闪的高风亮节
to violate your delicate sensibilities.
詹妮弗
Jennifer!
（警报启动 报警）
詹妮弗
Jennifer!
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
詹妮弗
Jennifer!
小心你的背后
Look out behind you!
琼
Joan!
不要
No!
搞定
Done!
听着 我不会责怪你的
Look, I'm not going to give you crap.
人无完人 蒂凡尼
Nobody is perfect, Tiff.
我自己也在壁橱里藏了些尸体
I got a few skeletons in the closet myself.
看见了吗？
See?
行了 好了 蒂凡尼
Well, come on, Tiff.
罗马建成需要多长时间 管他呢？
How long did it take to build Rome, anyway?
蒂凡尼
Tiff.
格林？
Glen?
在猜一次 老爸
Guess again, Daddy.
格琳达？
Glenda?
这才是我的名字
That's my name.
难道你不喜欢吗？
Don't you wear it out?
哦 见鬼
Oh, shit.
我错过了什么？
What did I miss?
哦 没啥 我刚刚烧死了琼
Oh, nothing much. I just fired Joan.
看来最后还是你赢了 蒂凡尼
Looks like you win after all, Tiff.
恭喜啦
Congratulations.
哦 你俩都赢了
Oh, you both win.
我真的是一位少女杀手
I'm a real lady-killer
如果你们懂我的意思
if you catch my drift.
我是一个无知的小丫头
I'm a bona fide bonus baby.
老天啊 恰吉 你对他做了什么？
Jesus Christ, Chucky, what did you do to him?
我做了什么？
What did I do?
嗯
Hmm.
我起码陪孩子一起玩过
At least I spent time with the kid.
格林 醒醒
Glen, wake up.
消停会儿吧 妈妈
Stop it, Mommy.
你会把我的裙子弄皱的
You'll wrinkle my dress.
哦 你喜欢吗？
Oh, and how do you like it?
我自己做的
I made it myseif.
有其母 必有其女 对不？
Like mother, like daughter, right?
有其母 必有其女
Like mother, like daughter.
懂了吗？母女 母女 母女
Get it? "Mother and daughter."
我说 醒醒 快醒醒
I said, wake up! Right now.
老妈？老爸？
Mom? Dad?
我这是怎么回事？
What am I?
用力 泰莉小姐 用力
Push, Miss Tilly. Push.
我正在用力 你这个混蛋小魔星
I am pushing, you little star-fucker!
别在意这位脏话连篇妹
Pay no attention to little Miss Potty Mouth.
她就是这样
She's hormonal.
天啊 要出来了
My God. It's coming.
我都能看到他的小脑袋了
I can see its little head.
男孩女孩？男孩女孩？
What is it? What is it?
是个男孩
It's a boy.
男孩？
A boy?
哦 谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
把孩子给我
Give me my baby.
我想看看我的孩子
I want my baby.
恰吉 恰吉 呃 还没生完呢
Chucky, Chucky, uh, well, we're not done here yet.
什么？
What?
詹妮弗还没有生完呢
Jennifer isn't done.
还有一个小宝宝没出来
We've got another one here!
用力 詹妮弗 用力 用力
Push, Jennifer! Push! Push, push.
把它挤出来 挤出来
Push it out! Push!
这个是什么？
What's this one?
是个女孩
It's a girl.
太棒了
Groovy.
啊 呀 呀 呀
Ai, yai, yai, yai, yai.
恰吉 是时候了
Chucky, it's time.
[咒语]
我祈求你 赐予我力量吧
Give me the power, I beg of you.
恰吉 他必须得选一个
Chucky, first he has to choose.
你说什么？
I beg your pardon.
抱歉 她必须得选一个
I'm sorry. She has to choose.
没时间管这屁事了
We don't have time for this shit!
等等 恰吉
Wait, Chucky.
我们现在有了一个儿子和一个女儿
We have a son and a daughter.
格林和格琳达
Glen and Glenda.
你懂了吗？
Don't you get it?
或许神明都用不着筛选了
Maybe they don't have to choose.
救命啊
Help!
快 恰吉 快念咒语
Hurry, Chucky! Do the chant.
恰吉 快点念咒
Chucky, do it now!
救救我们
Help us!
恰吉 你傻站着那干嘛？
Chucky, what are you standing there for?
念咒语啊
Do the chant!
还等什么呢？快点念咒语
What are you waiting for? Do it!
念咒语
Do the chant!
念啊
Do it!
都给我统统 闭嘴
Everybody just shut up!
我受够了 够了
I have had it! That's it!
我们时间有限
There is a limit to how much I can take.
你说什么？
What are you talking about?
看看你的周围 蒂凡尼 这太疯狂了
Look around you, Tiff. This is nuts.
我也很能容忍你这些疯狂举动
And I have a very high tolerance for nuts.
如果这只是会让我们成为人类
If this is what it takes to be human,
那我宁可选择我的机遇
then I would rather take my chances
成为一个天生疯狂的超级娃娃
as a supernaturally possessed doll.
可比成为人类简单的多
It's less complicated.
你不会是认真的吧？
You can't be serious?
是发自内心的
As a heart attack.
想想吧
Think about it.
成为人类有什么好的 各方面？
What is so great about being human, anyway?
你会生病 你会衰老
You get sick. You get old.
最后爬都爬不起来
You can't get it up anymore.
我可不期待成为那样
I'm not looking forward to that.
但是我只是想成为詹妮弗·泰莉
But I want to be Jennifer Tilly.
我想成为明星
I want to be a star.
那我不想成为你的司机
And I don't want to be your chauffeur.
作为一个娃娃 我他妈的声名狼藉
As a doll, I'm fucking infamous.
我是历史上最富盛名的杀手之一
I'm one of the most notorious slashers in history.
然而我不想放弃这些
And I don't want to give that up.
我是恰吉 王牌的娃娃杀手
I am Chucky, the killer doll!
我已经做到了
And I dig it!
我有我想要的一切
I have everything I want:
一位漂亮的妻子
A beautiful wife,
一个天生丽质的孩子
a multi-talented kid.
这才是真正的我 蒂凡尼
This is who I am, Tiff.
这才是我
This is me.
恰吉 我不懂
Chucky, I don't know
你他妈的在说些什么
what the fuck you're talking about.
我也不知道你他妈的到底是谁
I don't know who the fuck you are anymore.
但是对于我来说还不够
But it's not enough for me.
我要的更多
I want more.
你说什么？
What are you sayin'?
结束了
It's over.
你先出去 小心肝
You've got to get out of here, Sweetface.
我要离开你 恰吉 我要带走孩子
I'm leaving you, Chucky, and I'm taking the kid.
没人能离开我
Nobody leaves me.
没人
Nobody!
不要
No!
詹妮弗
Jennifer,
我爱
I love…
斯坦 说出来 说出来
Stan, tell me. Tell me…
我爱…
I love…
什么？
What?
上帝啊
Jesus.
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我的孩子 把孩子给我
My babies. Give me my babies.
我只想知道他们在哪
I just want to know where they are.
他们很好 詹妮弗
They're fine, Jennifer.
他们都在婴儿护理室里
They're in the maternity ward.
那好 有那么难吗？
All right, was that so hard?
现在最重要的是你要好好恢复
The important thing to think about now is getting well
这样你才能继续你的生活和事业
so you can get on with your life and your career.
我不关心我的事业
I don't care about my career.
我想要我的孩子
I want my babies.
我正在办这件事 詹妮弗 但是不是那么容易
I'm working on it, Jennifer, but you're not making it easy.
我已经和警察谈过了
I already talked to the cops.
他们释放我了
They cleared me.
他们知道你是清白的
They know you're not a killer.
但是没说你是头脑清醒的
They didn't say you were mentally competent.
你别指望着 他们会相信你讲的那个故事
Now what do you expect, after the story you told them
那是真的
It's true.
是的 好吧 我建议你从现在开始什么也别说了
Yeah, well, I suggest from now on you keep that to yourself.
嗯？
Hmm?
我们过会儿在谈
We'll talk later.
睡会觉吧
Try to get some sleep.
祝我好运吧 小心肝
Wish me luck, Sweetface.
妈妈就要成为明星了
Mommy is going to be a star.
我简直无话可说了
I can't think of a thing to say.
去他妈的
Fuck it!
[咒语]
我祈求你 赐予我力量吧
Give me the power, I beg of you.
[咒语]
移魂 移魂
Switch! Switch!
移魂 移魂 移魂
Switch! Switch! Switch!
没人能离开我 没人
Nobody leaves me. Nobody.
妈妈
Okasan.
我想你成为一个好女孩
I want you to be a good girl
或者男孩 什么都行
or boy. Whatever.
不要再重蹈你爸爸和妈妈的覆辙
Don't make the same mistakes your mom and dad made.
特别是你爸爸的
Especially your dad.
（谢谢你 妈妈）
来吧
Let's go.
格琳达？
Glenda?
不 老爸 是我 你儿子
No, Dad! It's me! Your boy!
送您归西的好儿子
Your chip off the old block!
你现在为我自豪吧 老爸
Are you proud of me now, Daddy?
自豪吗？
Are you?
好儿子 孩子 真是好儿子
Attaboy, kid. Attaboy.
放松 放松
There, there.
没事了 没事了
都会好起来的
It's all right.
会好起来的
一切都会好起来的
It's going to be all right.
没事了 没事了
There, there.
会好起来的
It's all right.
（五年后）
昨天 她把达纳·谢尔顿的鼻子弄出血了
Yesterday, she gave Dana Shelton a bloody nose
然后还照了照片四处张扬
and took pictures of it for Show and Tell.
她给那只猫取了个脏话名字（Cock：男人生殖器）
She called the cat the "C" word.
还有我十分肯定她从我包里偷过钱
And I'm pretty sure she's been taking money from my purse.
太滑稽了吧
That's ridiculous.
格林 他是个天使
Glen, he is an angel.
所有家长的梦想
An absolute dream.
但是格琳达
But Glenda,
她是个坏女孩 泰莉小姐
she's a bad girl, Miss Tilly.
一个非常坏的女孩
A very bad girl.
我不想听这些
I'm not listening to this.
哦 我讨厌这个东西
Oh, I hate that thing.
但是许多孩子真的很想见见她呢
Some of the kids really want to see her.
泰莉小姐
Miss Tilly.
什么事？
What?
我怕她
I'm afraid of her.
哦 弗维娅 一个娃娃而已嘛
Oh, Fulvia, it's only a doll.
我是在说格琳达
I was talking about Glenda.
弗维娅
Fulvia,
能把你的话说的直白点吗？
just exactly what are you trying to say?
我不能在这干了
I can't work here anymore.
为什么？
What?
对不起 就是不能
I'm sorry, I just can't…
你可以看看她看我的眼神里
If you only saw the way she looks at me,
充满了仇恨
with such hate.
好吧 弗维娅 如果你想这样做的话
All right, Fulvia, if that's what you want.
我们会想念你的
We'll miss you.
谢谢 泰莉小姐 愿上帝保佑你
Thank you, Miss Tilly. God bless.
呃
Hmm.
保佑你妹啊
God bless.
犯个小错而已
Just a little slip.
罗马也不是一天建成的 你知道的
Rome wasn't built in a day, you know.
我们都会遇到一些小挫折
We all have our little setbacks.
我不是一个坏人 只不过是做点坏事而已
I'm not a bad person. I just do bad things.
嘘
Shs…
妈妈终于如愿了
Mom got her wish.
她现在是一颗耀眼的明星
She's a bright shining star.
现在我们的家庭很完美
Now we're the perfect family.
我自己也学会了很多事
I've learned a lot about myself.
我知道我并不孤独
I know I'm not alone.
也知道我并不是怪胎
I know I'm not a freak.
虽然我们还是有一些不同
And even though we had our differences,
我也知道爸爸真的很爱我的
I know my dad really loved me.
哦 格林
Oh, Glen.
格林 小心肝 来这里
Glen, sweetheart, come over here.
这 小心肝 看
Here, sweetheart, look.
这还有件礼物
Here's another one.
谁送的 妈妈？
Who is it from, Mommy?
不知道
I don't know.
嗯 看看吧 哦 上面没有写
Hmm, let's see. Oh, it doesn't say.
好奇怪 上面没说是谁送的
Strange. It doesn't say who it is.
拜拜 心肝 别跑的太远
Bye, sweetheart. Don't run so fast.
等会还要出发去旅游的
You're going to trip.
随便吧 他自己都决定好了何时出发
So anyway, he determined that he was going to go off…